I'll tell her how I feel.
Okay, here I go.
What's Raven doing here, anyway?
Wait, don't tell me the
girl he likes is...
Cecilia?!
Oh, no! Did I just give a
supportive nudge to a rival?!
No, wait! Surely Cecilia wouldn't
accept him that easily!
Oh, but they were in the hero's
party together, weren't they?!
So maybe, just maybe...
Cecilia, I'll protect you.
Raven... I trust you.
What if something like that happened?!
Raven?
How'd it go?
You encouraged me, and still... I'm sorry.
I'll just die.
Did you forget something, Master Yoki?
I just, um...
I was wondering how Cecilia was doing!
Pardon?
I was just here to visit her!
I must look so suspicious right now!
Milady has retired for the night.
DENIED
Please come back on another day.
Um, Raven was just here, wasn't he?
Sir Raven? Yes, he was just here.
He asked to see Happiness.
Huh?
The one he confessed to was...
Happiness?!
Hey.
What?
Didn't Raven... I mean, a guy
with red hair come to see you?
He's a friend of mine.
He, um... told you he liked you, right?
How did you answer?
"Impossible."
Wow, she shot him right down.
I-I see. Not a chance, huh?
Well, can't help it if you don't like him.
No.
Huh? Then why is it impossible?
And where did you meet
him in the first place?
Impossible.
Hey!
I'll try again later.
So on that note...
I would like us to discuss
Raven and Happiness!
Who's Raven?
A swordsman from the hero's party.
Oh!
That human who was
constantly losing to you!
Captain, why did you allow a
human to get close to Happiness?
Hey, relax. I didn't introduce them.
I can't imagine Happiness feeling good
about having a human say he likes her.
Harpies are naturally attractive.
There are countless humans
who'd capture them to make them slaves
or steal their beautiful feathers.
In fact, I joined the Demon King's army
after I saved Happiness when she
was being chased by some humans.
That's true.
I don't think Happy actually
hates humans, though.
I mean, some humans are nice.
Happy decided to be a maid because she
liked the people in that house, right?
Yeah, that's right.
I get why you're concerned, Duke,
but Raven isn't a bad guy.
I think Happiness realizes that, too.
Huh?
Kramen isn't here today?
Excuse me.
Aren't you the gentleman I always see
speaking with the vice guildmaster?
The vice guildmaster?
Yes.
Uh, who?
I'm talking about our
vice guildmaster, Kramen.
Huh?!
He's the vice guildmaster?!
Whatever.
I can see why you'd react that way.
So... where is he, anyway?
It's a matter that could endanger
the guild's dignity,
so I can't say it too loudly, but...
he's in the hospital.
What?!
Hey, Vice Guildmaster.
What's this? You came to visit me?
Well, thanks.
You're hurt pretty bad. What happened?
I pissed off the wife.
Huh?
His wife?!
It was our wedding
anniversary the other day.
I was trying to choose a gift for her,
but I was having trouble deciding.
I wasted so much time thinking about it,
I missed my chance to buy anything.
And then I didn't even
make it home for dinner,
so she thought I'd forgotten
about our anniversary...
and ended up like this.
Hospitalized after a fight with the wife?
I can see why that would
make the guild look bad.
Your wife must be really strong.
Well, she's a former A-Rank adventurer.
Rank A?!
As am I, by the way.
We used to work as a duo.
The nickname we earned as we took on
high-ranked quests together was...
the Invincible Apathy Couple.
I could not be less
envious of that nickname.
I'll use healing magic on
you to heal your wounds.
No need!
This is my chance to get my wife
to nurse me back to health.
Don't butt in.
I'm not sure why, but... I'm sorry.
How are you feeling, dear?
I brought a change of clothes.
Oh, Master Yoki.
Sophia?!
Wait, so your wife is...
I've been waiting for you, honey!
Who are you calling "honey"?
You always call me "Sophia."
I saw up your skirt.
That's fine.
It is?!
He is my husband, after all.
Thank you for coming to visit my husband.
Nah, it's fine.
Um, how is Cecilia doing?
Her fever has gone down.
She's all right now.
Oh, good.
Um... may I go see her today?
She is out running various
errands for the day.
I would have preferred for her
to rest a few more days, but...
She's pretty busy, huh?
So, um...
Yes?
I guess getting gifts is pretty
important to girls, then?
Did my husband tell you something?
Oh, not really... but maybe sort of...
I want to do something
that'll make Cecilia happy.
As long as your heart is truly in
it, I'm sure she'll be pleased.
Thank you! See you later!
Husband and wife, huh?
That sounds so nice.
If I were to marry Cecilia...
is this how it'd be?
Dinner is ready, dear!
Or maybe...
this?
I'm sorry I came home late, Yoki.
I'm so hungry!
Wait, why are these set
in my previous life?!
So this is the knights' dorm?
Raven?
I'm coming in...
Are you okay? Hey.
Happiness.
Yoki? How do you know that name?
Welcome back, Raven.
I've known her for ages, actually.
So I couldn't help wondering, you know?
Would you mind telling
me how this all happened?
Okay.
It started one day when I was
out patrolling on my own...
Hey, little lady, why
don't you come with us?
Who the hell are you?
Quit staring, you scrawny little runt!
Dude, he's Raven from the knight order!
From the hero's party?!
Tch. Let's go.
Thanks.
It's my job.
Nice voice.
What?
I said, "Nice voice."
Don't be crazy. It doesn't
match how I look at all.
Doesn't matter.
I envy you.
Thank you. Bye.
The uniform she was
wearing looked familiar.
So that's why you came
to Cecilia's mansion.
You know Cecilia, too?
Yeah, well... you could say that.
You're amazing, Yoki.
You left your home to be
with the one you love,
and you're working hard as an
adventurer to be a man worthy of her.
Yeah, something like that.
Compared to you, I'm...
Oh, come on! Don't be so down!
Happiness is just, well... not
great at dealing with men.
Part of it comes from some past trauma.
I see. I must have frightened her by
confessing with such careless haste.
I don't think that's it.
It's just my baseless opinion, but...
I think it's too soon to give up just yet.
Okay, Raven, you and I
are going out on the town!
Huh?
Aren't we a bit out of place here?
It's fine, I promise.
Oh, good! It's still here!
I hope Cecilia will like it.
Thank you very much.
Looks perfect for Happiness.
You think so?
Why not buy it for her?
Wouldn't getting a gift from a man
she barely knows only frighten her?
You just don't get it, Raven.
As long as your heart is truly
in it, it'll make her happy.
C-Can I trust that?
Not to mention it's a design
Happiness would probably like.
If I do have a chance to see her again...
I'LL TAKE THIS.
Uh... Of course. That'll be all, then?
Is it a gift?
He speaks in written form
since he can't use his voice?
Thank you very much.
What? Swordsman?
And you're the civilian I saw
with the priestess last time.
I'm impressed a couple of men would
come here on their own.
We were just picking out some gifts, okay?
Yeah? For who?
For the girls we love, of course!
Oh? I knew you had your
eye on the priestess,
but I didn't know about the swordsman.
Sorry, Raven!
Still refusing to talk, I see.
I know it's my own fault for laughing
at you when we first met, but...
Wait, what? She has a sharp
tongue, but she regrets that?
Let's go somewhere else.
I want to hear more.
Hey! Who said you could...
WE CAN'T GET AWAY. JUST GIVE UP.
Okay, we can take our time chatting here.
Wait, you two...
have no intention of
talking to me, do you?
It's Operation You Can't Talk
While Eating, so Keep Quiet!
Now we can't say anything.
Aw... and here I was going to give
you some intel about the priestess.
Please do.
How easy are you?!
So? How far have you gotten
with the priestess?
Well, we're not going out or anything,
and she's gotten marriage offers
from all over the place...
Like from Yuga?
She said she turned him down.
Of course she did. That idiot
is constantly angering her.
Like barging in when we're changing...
Morning!
or getting his bath time wrong
so we run into each other...
Hello!
To make it worse, he's
so popular with women
that it hinders our travels.
Guys, let's stay in this town one
more night, for these ladies' sakes.
Hero.
You are far too loose with women.
The priestess is serious trouble
when she's angry, you know.
You'd better watch yourself.
G-Got it...
Okay, now you tell me about the swordsman.
I will defend the pure
love in Raven's heart!
Why are you making me out
to be the villain here?!
You're not?
Believe it or not, I was
hoping I could help somehow.
Besides... sometimes you just want
to talk about that stuff, y'know?
YOU NEED SOME LOVE ADVICE, TOO?
Th-This isn't about me or anything...
YOKI'S A GUY YOU CAN DEPEND ON.
Really?
Okay, fine. The thing is...
I've made Yuga hate me.
Because of something that happened.
You know, don't you, swordsman?
This sounds like a pretty
delicate subject.
Hey, can you swear you
won't tell anyone else?
Sure. I promise.
Our hero's party...
was defeated several times
at the Demon King's castle.
Oh! Y-You were?
I know that!
And not even by the Demon King.
The demon guarding the middle part
of the castle was really strong.
He made complete fools of us.
Every time we lost,
we were carried back
to the nearest village.
They were even so kind
as to heal our wounds.
It was humiliating.
I know that, too!
But...
the thing is, we lied.
We told people we turned back
in the middle of the castle
to make sure we were ready.
All of their hopes were
riding on the hero's party,
so we did it to protect our honor... and
most of all, that of Yuga's as hero.
We kept losing for a month straight.
The village was running low on supplies.
We couldn't keep falsifying
our reports any longer.
It was all over.
And then...
that demon made us an offer.
Leave the priestess here.
Do that, and I will let
the other three pass.
I was the one who convinced the
others to agree to his terms.
I guess Yuga can't forgive me
for making such a cruel choice.
He won't say so, and
he still acts cheerful,
but I can just tell.
You can't forgive me either, can you?
Huh?
I almost killed the priestess
you love so much.
Uh...
Yoki, don't blame Mikana.
You... Your voice...
I'm partly to blame myself
for not voicing my opinion.
Mikana...
I'm sorry.
Forget blaming her.
I never realized I'd created
such a rift in the hero's party.
Hey... did you guys ever
tell Cecilia how you feel?
What am I supposed to tell her?
That I sacrificed our priestess
to protect Yuga's honor because
I was in love with him?
I can't expect her to forgive
me just because I say I'm sorry.
So you're just going to let
things stay awkward forever?
You really want things to stay this way?
Why don't you give it
a little more thought?
You're right. I can't
leave things like this.
What the heck? For having such a
dull face, you're pretty useful.
Part of that was unnecessary.
I don't want things to end this way.
I'm going to go see Happiness again.
Oh, Captain.
Huh? What are you guys doing here?
Shiek insisted on seeing Celia.
Who's this?
Oh, this is Raven.
This is the man who
confessed to Happiness?
What have you come here for?
Making a move again after
she rejected you once?
That's pretty pathetic!
Hey, cut it out.
Sorry, Raven.
Duke's known Happiness for a long time,
so he worries about her.
What is it you're after?
I won't allow anyone to try to approach
Happiness with evil intentions!
Silence?!
If you're not going to talk, then go away!
I can't entrust my precious
companion to a wimp like you!
Hey! Raven is...
I don't know anything about Happiness.
I don't even know what I
should do when I see her.
What?!
Shouldn't you say "I'll protect you"
or "I'll make you happy" or something?
Those wouldn't be my words.
Oh! Happy!
Then go and speak your own words to her!
I will.
Come on, man...
I was just testing him a little.
Happiness needs to think
about this for herself, too.
I'm sorry about last time.
Um... here.
Um... c-can...
Can we be friends?
If it's just friends...
Thank you, Happiness.